owntitle.com 2017-11-12

# Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy applies to information we collect about you at [www.owntitle.com](https://www.owntitle.com/) (the "Website") and OwnTitle applications and how the information will be used. 

## Collection of your Information

Your information gathered or received as you visit OwnTitle includes technical information which does not directly identify you. Such information collected, without limitation includes: (a) the type of browser you are using (e.g., Chrome, Internet Explorer), (b) the type of operating system you are using (e.g., Windows or Mac OS), (c) your manner of connecting to the Internet (e.g., connection speed through narrowband or broadband access); (d) which pages and content are browsed, interactions with advertising and content, and other data related to preferences and usage. 

OwnTitle collects emails for newsletters only when users submit their email of their own free will, to require timely notification on new movie release information and movie news. OwnTitle do not collect personal name and will not identify you when you submitting Email address. 

While OwnTitle currently do not provide any account registration and any other personal information required services to visitors, there will be no personal security information risks involved during visiting OwnTitle. 

##  How we use your information

As we cannot and will not identify you by collecting your browsing information, we use this information including, without limitation, to serve better content to you, to better target advertising and content, to generate statistics, reports and for various analytic purposes. 

The email we collect is submitted by your own free will, and we use email address for newsletters purpose only. Newsletter including the general movie / TV show release date alert, advertisement and movie news only. We don’t collect any more personal information together with emails, and we will never disclose user email information to any third party. 

##  Cookies, Web Beacons and Similar Technologies

Cookies are text files that are placed in your computer's browser, and that can be used to help recognize you as a OwnTitle user. Web beacons are small pieces of code placed on Web pages that can be used, among other things, to count the users who visit that Web page, or to deliver a cookie to the browser of a user viewing that page. You can control cookies through your browser's settings. If you reject all cookies, however, you might not get user-friendly and targeted recommendations. Cookie helps personalize your experience on OwnTitle. 

## Advertisement 

We use third party ad services to display interest-based ads on our site. These ads may contain cookies and/or web beacons to collect data in the ad serving process and are collected by our ad companies, we do not have access to this information. We work with the ad companies: Google. Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on our site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to our users based on their visit to our sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [ google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/). 

## Security

OwnTitle only display Movie information such as basic plot introduction, trailers, cast, etc. We do not provide movie download accesses or any other downloadable files. OwnTitle is devoted to provide a clean website to you and protect users from any harmful malwares. 

## COPPA

OwnTitle is intended for a general audience and is not intended for children under 13 and also we could not directly identify them as children under 13. We are especially concerned about protecting children’s privacy. Therefore, we comply with the Children’s Online Privacy Protection Act of 1998 (COPPA) and its accompanying Federal Trade Commission regulation establish United States Federal law that protects the privacy of children using the Internet. We DO NOT and WILL NOT collect any private information from children under the age of 13 through website or in any other manners. 

## Changes to this Privacy Policy and Additional Information

We may update this Privacy Policy from time to time, and so you are welcomed to review this Policy periodically. If there are significant changes to the website's information practices, we will provide appropriate online notice on the website. 

Last Updated: June 16, 2017
